Uladzimir Akulovich

https://www.linkedin.com/in/uladzimir-akulovich/ uladzimir.akulovich@gmail.com +372 5366-3476

I'm an **Android Developer**, specializing in *Kotlin*. My experience includes working with Coroutines, Jetpack Compose, RxJava, and Android Architecture Components.

I'm originally from Minsk, Belarus, but I live in Tallinn, Estonia.

EXPERIENCE

Bolt Technology OÜ, Tallinn, Estonia

April 2021 - July 2022 Software Engineer

August 2022 - PRESENT Senior Software Engineer

Android app for Drivers.

- Feature leading of earnings goal feature.
- Markers and polygons on the map.
- Switch between speakerphone and Bluetooth handset.

ScienceSoft, Minsk, Belarus - Android Developer

November 2014 - February 2021

Chat & VoIP App. March 2016 - January 2021. Java, RxJava, Android Architecture Components

- "Voice Notes" messages.
- File messages.

Mobile Banking App. November 2014 - January 2016. Java, RxJava

- A tablet version of the app.
- "Personal Financial Manager" feature financial reports, including charts.
- Chat with customer support.

EPAM Systems, Minsk, Belarus – Android Developer

January 2013 - November 2014

Car & Dealers Catalog.

Marketing App.

EDUCATION

Belarussian State University, Minsk, Belarus - Bachelor

2008 - 2013, Faculty of Applied Mathematics and Computer Science

KEYWORDS

Kotlin, Jetpack Compose, Coroutines, RxJava, Retrofit, Protobuf.